It really looks good even when you go to bed.
本当に寝に来ても似合うね
This doesn't suit me right away.
これ早々似合わないよ
I'm so happy.
嬉しいっしょ
And it just so happens that it doesn't have any hair.
しかもちょうどよく毛がないからさ
If there's any hair on this, it'll definitely come out around here.
これ 絶対毛あったらここらへんから出るからね
That's no good.
ダ メ だよね
good.
よかった
Is Misa-chan losing her hair?
ミサちゃん脱毛してるの?
I'm losing my hair.
脱毛してるよ
It was okay.
大丈夫だった
good.
よ かった
Chikuri is so beautiful.
ちくりすごい綺麗だね
I didn't see much of it just now.
さっきあんまり見れなかったけど
You're smaller than me, Newlin.
俺よりちっちゃいじゃん、ニューリン
That's not true.
そんなことない
Chi
ち
I can feel it.
く り感じちゃう
Super subtle.
超微妙
Is it okay?
いいの?
Can you meet me outside the store?
店の外で会ってくれる?
Don't tell me.
内緒だよ
Of course I'll go to the store.
もちろんちゃんとお店に行くけどさ
It's okay if you don't tell me.
内緒ならいいよ
Because it's a secret.
秘密だからね
Seriously, once you know this, you're in trouble.
これをさ、一回知ったらもうやばいってまじで
Yeah.
うん
Misa-chan, I also like chikuri.
ミサちゃん俺もさ、ちくり好きなのね
Yeah.
うん
Misa Chikurimosa, I played around with it a little bit.
ミ サちくりもさ、ちょっといじったり
Can you imitate me?
真似たりしてくれない?
Yeah.
うん
Amazing people.
すごい人遣い
Where have you ever licked your tongue?
どこにとんちくみ舐めたことあった?
yes.
そう
Yeah.
うん
Amazing people.
すごい人遣い
Lick it again and go inside.
また舐めて、うちに行ってみて
good?
いい?
It seems so.
そうやらしい
Being licked.
舐められる
That's amazing.
すごいね
Can you lick me all the time?
ずっと舐められるの?
so.
そんなに
You definitely lent me a lot with your mouth.
絶対口でいっぱい貸してきたでしょ
Yeah.
うん
Because I said it in a teasing manner.
せいしなじして言ってたから
hey.
ね
Because it felt amazing.
すごい 気持ちかったから
Is it okay?
いいの?
いい の?
I was let in.
入れてもらった
good?
いい?
I was let in.
入 れてもらった
Please lie down for a moment.
ちょっと横になってくれ
I want to put it in right away.
すぐに入れたくなっちゃう
It felt amazing just now.
気持ちかったもん、すごいさっき
You can see Ensanto's Santo mark on this.
これ、 アンサントさんの サントマーク見れちゃおう
Do this, do this,
こう やって、 こう やって、
In this way, quickly
こう やって、 す ぐ
I fell asleep.
寝 ちゃった
My current position is terrible.
今の体勢やばくて
I fell asleep faster than before.
さっきよりすぐ寝ちゃった
It was a medical examination.
診察でした
That was great.
よかったですね
Be careful.
気をつけして
Yeah.
うん
I fell asleep.
寝ちゃったね
I fell asleep after saying that.
言ってたから寝ちゃった